You have no idea what was happening out here
And uh
It's got the right time and
Hey
Get to cover right
Let's go go right
Hop down
Hop out
Stay down
What is he saying to go under the under the bridge
Gonna get that fit ready
We got this one ready
Yeah um
Should we fully prep them
We got artillery
We should probably not be the same spot here
They would hit the bridge one day
Yeah
This thing's very chilling out there at the moment
What do we do now
We us
That's overhead
Yeah
The train artilery
We're in the middle
I want to explain what's going on
We got villagers back there
Yes
We got villagers
Uh
About a kilometer back
Say
About a kilometer in front
We got russian in front
We got arty
Thanks
Raining down on us well
They're raining down on us
And the villagers bro
We're honestly
We got to get to the village
Being out here is not gonna do any good
Yep
Go tell him all right
Where the is ivan
Where's ivan
He went for
With the chlike
What are we doing here
Then we're soaking up artillery by the looks of it
All right
Here but a little damp go go go go go no no no no no no
That's just right and run
How much are you
Oh
You get that out of there
No no
We go by the way
We wait for the other cowboy
Let's go
Ba ba ba
So we are what's up
What's up
We're gonna go kill
Inside your house
Get inside
We gotta sit down
Good
Let's get that good side
Go go go go go
All right
I'm gonna open up this door
You get in
You said jet
Yeah
It's jet that ours who knows
Okay
You got five jets on the jet
That's the fact
Digits
And if they're fighting there
Bro
I believe you ain't a man
You know
Yeah
If you're finding there
Then we're we can't go back
They're just gonna open it up on us
I think we're gonna have to walk it
Bro yeah no
I think we walk it
Doc
My duck
No
It does not sound like a birector
I've had this flyover every day
And yhey
Let's spread out spread
Yeah
That's got to be one of ours
Though
I don't know man
Yeah
I don't like the space anyway
No
It's not
Yeah
It's ours
I think so
Yeah
It's getting ready to hop
So the woman
There's a person with a red shirt right
That's occupied for so far
I think it's occupied
There is you have like a map
A map carta
Uh
Get get a killer over here
Keller
Get two people four hundred meters away directly right black
Yes
Let's meet
They were moving
And then they stopped
Hey
Do we have binos
Binos
Over here
Yeah
We need to get that covered
I think that's
Uh
I think that's wrong
Or just guards
But you saw him
They stopped
Yeah
They stood up
They moved the concealment and look black
Which means uniforms
Oh
Back down
Do not
Hey
There can be more
Man
They're going ham
That's not cash money
You need them
God damn
That was up my boys intact about it
That'll be a mission for a litter
Damn it
Yeah
Was this my lid on me
Oh
Hold on
Hope you stay down
I want you to know
No
You can see it
Dude
I'm gonna close up the door
Does everyone have everything they need out of the vehicle
I'm leaving the aid bag inside
Watch out for hey
There's down power lines right here
Just watch it
This is good good spot
Really good spot
Yeah
And we can still see it there
Nice one
Booster
Can you keep an eye out for a today sucks
Yeah
Today really sucks well
It's normal bunker
Yeah
Dude
It's cool
He gets to go chill over there
That are we driving on the wrong road no
This is not the right road
Dude
It's not the right road
Yeah
We should probably turn around
This is where
Where the impacts are coming
Yeah
There we go
Our road didn't have any prom
This is towards the front
I just remember we had the turn really close to us
Remember i can go straight out
Yeah
Just be a rodeo
Okay
Come on
That's mine right there
It seems like what do you think
When you scare the
Hey
They're falling back all the way
Yeah
Let's go moving
Hey
Roger there
You're watching it
I need the dirt
I put it on after that
You guys remember my last mission in ukraine a year ago
Near the city of balkthea was planting mines
And in this particular area
This happens all the time
So